BRITTINY CARVAJAL

PROFLE

Former tax liens specialist turned UI/UX Designer with experience working with clientele to meet their needs as an individual and as a target audience. Passionate about searching for solutions and creating products that cater to and excite users.

916.990.3276

BrittinyCarvajal@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/brittiny-carvajal/ https://www.behance.net/brittinycarvajal Lehi, UT

SKILLS Tools

Sketch Branding

InVision Research

Wireframes Flinto

Adobe XD User Personas

User Testing Zeplin

SPECIAL PROJECTS

Artist, Graphite, Oil Pastels, and Rip Art

Interior Decorator, CA Created artwork for clients

Play Notes Designer, BYU-I La Boheme Opera Production

Editor, BYU-I Robotics Textbook by Paul Johnson

EDUCATION

UI Design

CareerFoundry, 3/2019-7/2019

Web Development

CareerFoundry, 6/2019-Present

English, Professional Writing

BYU-Idaho, 9/2013-4/2015

AA, Social and Behavioral Sciences

Folsom Lake College, 8/2011-5/2013

EXPERIENCE

Transfer Program Coordinator

Zulu Marketing, Lehi, UT, 5/2018-6/2019

- Supervised coworkers by helping develop their efficiency increasing completed transfers by 150%.
- Created effective communication lanes with vendors reducing transfer time by 30%.

Event Coordinator

Network Environmental Systems, Folsom, CA, 9/2017-3/2018

- Advanced branding established on company blog bringing more clients.
- Negotiated and coordinated with clients improving coworkers time-management and client's experience.

Administrative Assistant

Bickmore, Sacramento, CA, 4/2016-1/2017

- Oversaw timely correspondences growing clientele.
- Solved client cases against their county producing 50+ processed claims.
- Assisted others generating a stronger team setting.

Research Associate

Research and Business Development Center, Rexburg, ID, 9/2015-12/2015

- Marketed Motorfist brand with 3 different surveys, updating user-friendly website and other media in order to understand the snowmobile industry in depth and how to help Motorfist increase.
- Pitched project findings to Motorfist creators which resulted in client growth by 20% and potential clientele by 40%.